<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on COLA-Lab@Exeter</title>
    <link>https://example.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on COLA-Lab@Exeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/projects/</guid>
      <description> Projects # Under construction </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive of COLA Seminar Series</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_seminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_seminar/</guid>
      <description> Archive of COLA Seminar Series # 2022 # </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive of Reading Group</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_reading/</guid>
      <description>Archive of Reading Group # Agenda (Year 2021) # June Learning from Multiple Cities: A Meta-Learning Approach for Spatial-Temporal Prediction
WWW 2019
paper | slides | Jiangjiao Xu | June 20
Bayesian temporal factorization for multidimensional time series prediction
IEEE PAMI 2021
paper | slides | Jiangjiao Xu | June 13
Discrete Fourier Transform and Random Fourier Features
Data-Driven Science and Engineering, Chapter 2: 47&amp;ndash;83, 2019
slides | Phoenix Williams | June 9</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive of Study Group</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_study/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/archive/archive_study/</guid>
      <description> Archive # 2022 # </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COLA Seminar Series</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/seminars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/seminars/</guid>
      <description>COLA Seminar Series # This is our seminar series where we exchange ideas with guest speakers, keeping you up to date with the latest developments and inspiring research topics. Occasionally, COLA researchers present their own work as well. Agenda (Year 2021) # June Exeter-Leiden Symposium on Data-Driven Modeling and Optimization
Website | Ke Li, Hao Wang | June 6 Previous seminar series can be found from our archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadlines</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/misc/ddl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/misc/ddl/</guid>
      <description> Deadlines # Here are some important deadlines for the major conferences in artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI &amp;amp; ML), data mining (DM), natural language processing (NLP), software engineering (SE) and evolutionary computation (EC) domains.
AI IJCAI 2023: January 18, 2022 ECAI 2023: TBD AAAI 2023: August 15, 2022 ICLR 2023: September 28, 2022 ML ICML 2023: January 26, 2022 ECML/PKDD 2023: TBD UAI 2022: February 25, 2022 NeurIPS 2022: May 17, 2022 AISTAS 2023: October 13, 2022 CV CVPR 2023: November 11, 2022 ICCV 2023: March 8, 2023 ECCV 2023: TBD DM KDD 2023: TBD ICDM 2023: July 1, 2023 SDM 2023: October 14, 2022 CIKM 2023: TBD NLP ACL 2022: November 15, 2021 NAACL 2022: Jan 15, 2022 COLING 2022: May 15, 2022 EMNLP 2022: May 24, 2022 SE ISSTA 2022: Jan 28, 2022 FSE 2023: February 2, 2022 ASE 2023: TBD ICSE 2024: March 29, 2023 (1st round) | August 1, 2023 (2nd round) EC GECCO 2023: TBD WCCI 2022: January 31, 2022 PPSN 2022: April 13, 2022 IJCNN 2022: February 10, 2022 CEC 2023: January 13, 2023 SMC 2023: March 30, 2023 FOGA 2022: May 7, 2022 SSCI 2023: TBD </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMOC</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/emoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/emoc/</guid>
      <description>EMOC stands for Evolutionary Multi-objective Optimization in C++ which is a framework for single-objective and multi-objective optimization.
For more information about installation and usage, please refer to the document site.
Features # Rich algorithms and problems
EMOC implemented about 30 algorithms and more than 80 test problems which both include single-objective and multi-objective types.
Developed in C++ and Cross-platform
All the source code of EMOC are wrote in C++. So the running efficiency is guaranteed when comparing other implementation with python, java or matlab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/grants/</guid>
      <description>Grants # We are grateful to have been generously supported by or closely working with the following funding bodies and industrial partners.
Ongoing Transfer Bayesian Optimization for Multi-Fidelity Data in Uncertain Environments
European Network Fund | #GP ENF5.10 | PI | £7,440 | 2021&amp;ndash;2022. Evolutionary Multi-Objective Search for Automating CNN Architecture Design
Royal Society | #IES\R2\212077 | PI | £11,815 | 2021&amp;ndash;2023. Human-Centric Computing
Alan Turing Fellowship | PI | 2021&amp;ndash;2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEEE DTEC</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/misc/dtec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/misc/dtec/</guid>
      <description>IEEE CIS Task Force 12 # Task Force on Decomposition-based Techniques in Evolutionary Computation Objectives # As the name suggests, the basic idea of the decomposition-based technique is to transform the original complex problem into simplified subproblem(s) so as to facilitate the optimization. Decomposition-based techniques have been widely used for solving both single- and multi-objective optimization problems. More specifically, in single-objective optimization, especially for the large-scale scenarios, which consider a tremendous amount of decision variables, the decomposition-based technique contains three aspects: 1) analyzing and understanding the fitness landscape and modularity structure of the underlying problem; 2) decomposing the original complex problem into several loosely coupled or independent subproblems based on the learnt characteristics; 3) using a meta-heuristic to solve these subproblems in a sequential or concurrent manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/members/</guid>
      <description>Members # Lookup table of acronyms in this page. &amp;#43; EMO: evolutionary multi-objective optimization BO: Bayesian optimization BLO: bi-level optimization MFO: multi-fidelity optimization CO: constrained optimization DO: dynamic optimization MCM: Monte Carlo method LA: landscape analysis TL: transfer learning MTL: multi-task learning LL: life-long learning GP: Gaussian processes NLP: natural language processing SE: software engineering VNF: virtual network functions Faculty # Dr Ke Li
UKRI FLF | Turing Fellow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/news/</guid>
      <description>News Archive # 2021 # Dec I have been invited to renew my term as an Associate Editor of IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation in 2022. Be humbled to serve our best journal in the evolutionary computation community. Dec 27 Nov Our paper &amp;ldquo;Distributed UAV Swarm Formation and Collision Avoidance Strategies Over Fixed and Switching Topologies&amp;rdquo; is accepted to IEEE Trans. Cybernetics. Congratulations to Jia! Nov 24 Oct I am proud to be recognized in the Top 2% Scientists Worldwide in a latest study from Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications # The copyrights of published papers are transferred to publishers. Misuse of any material posted here may result in plagiarism. + means my current/previous student or visitor. * means equal contribution To appear # Technical Report # A Data-Driven Evolutionary Transfer Optimization for Expensive Problems in Dynamic Environments
Ke Li*, Renzhi Chen+*, Xin Yao
CoRR abs/2211.02879 | November 2022
PDF | Supp | BiB @article{LiCY22, author = {Ke Li and Renzhi Chen and Xin Yao}, title = {A Data-Driven Evolutionary Transfer Optimization for Expensive Problems in Dynamic Environments}, journal = {CoRR}, volume = {abs/2211.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Group</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/readinggroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/readinggroup/</guid>
      <description>Reading Group # The paper reading group meets weekly during the semester to discuss papers. Participation is open to all, guests are always welcome; if you are interested in engaging with us, please feel free to contact Dr Ke Li. More about our reading group culture &amp;#43; The paper to discuss is announced about one week in advance by the presenter. All participants are expected to read the paper before the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Group</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/studygroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/studygroup/</guid>
      <description>Study Group # The core purpose of this study group, which runs every Sunday afternoon, is to learn some fundamental knowledge pertinent to our research. Participation is usually expected to be our COLA members. However, if you are interested in engaging with us, please feel free to contact Dr Ke Li for a discussion. Agenda (Year 2022) # Nov Nouns: plurals, countable versus uncountable
Academic Writing Series #1
slides | Ke Li | November 4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplementary</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/supp/supp_deto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/supp/supp_deto/</guid>
      <description>Supplementary Materials # This website maintains the supplementary materials related to the following paper:
Ke Li+, Renzhi Chen+, Xin Yao, &amp;ldquo;A Data-Driven Evolutionary Transfer Optimization for Expensive Problems in Dynamic Environments&amp;rdquo;, arXiv CoRR abs/xxxx.xxxxx, 2022. It consists of the following parts:
Appendix document of this paper can be found from our Dropbox link. Examples of the dynamically changing fitness landscape of both the moving peak benchmark problems (left hand side) and the moving peak benchmark with Gaussian peaks (right hand side).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplementary</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/supp/supp_dmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/supp/supp_dmi/</guid>
      <description>Supplementary Materials # This website maintains the supplementary materials related to the following paper:
Ke Li, Renzhi Chen, &amp;ldquo;Batched Data-Driven Evolutionary Multi-Objective Optimization Based on Manifold Interpolation&amp;rdquo;, IEEE Trans. Evol. Comput., accepted for publication, 2022. It consists of the following parts:
The source code of this paper can be found from our Github repo. Appendix document of this paper can be found from this Dropbox link. Tables of all comparison results can be found in this Dropbox link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symposium</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/events/activities/exeter_leiden_symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/events/activities/exeter_leiden_symposium/</guid>
      <description>Exeter-Leiden Symposium on Data-Driven Modeling and Optimization # Objectives # Data has been playing an ever-growing role in artificial/computational intelligence. Such role goes beyond its typical use in neural networks and learning systems, encompassing also evolutionary and other meta-heuristic optimization algorithms. The objective of this symposium is to provide a unique and vibrant cohort for sharing and experiencing the emerging methodologies and applications of data-driven artificial/computational intelligence. It will offer keynotes, invited lectures and discussion groups given by experts from Exeter, Leiden and other high-profile institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacancies</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/vacancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/vacancies/</guid>
      <description>Vacancies # We very much welcome and support applications from underrepresented groups and from people of all shapes, shades, and genders. If you are uncertain about your possible role in our team, please do not hesitate to get in touch with Ke Li.
PhD There are multiple opportunities available at the University of Exeter to fund your PhD study.
China Scholarship Council (Chinese Students): The University of Exeter is proud to offer up to 50 full-time PhD scholarships in collaboration with the China Scholarship Council (CSC).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
