<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on COLA-Lab@Exeter</title>
    <link>https://example.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on COLA-Lab@Exeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/archive_reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/archive_reading/</guid>
      <description>Archive of Reading Group #  Agenda (Year 2020) #  Dec   Surrogate Assisted Evolutionary Algorithms, Fan Li Dec 27
[slides]
  RoboGrammar: Graph Grammar for Terrain-Optimized Robot Design, ACM Trans. Graphics. Jiahao Zhou Dec 20
[paper] [slides]
  Optimization, Fast and Slow: Optimally Switching Between Local and Bayesian Optimization, ICML 2018. Guozhao Wei Dec 13
[paper] [slides]
  Nov   Ordinal Regression with Multiple Output CNN for Age Estimation, CVPR 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/bk_publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/bk_publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications #   hr.dashed { border-top: 1px dashed #bbb; } .grid-container { display: grid; grid-template-columns: 40% 60%; grid-gap: 5px; background-color: transparent; padding: 5px; }   The copyrights of published papers are transferred to publishers. Misuse of any material posted here may result in plagiarism. means equal contribution. + means student under my supervision. * means equal contribution   View by year #   ....  2020  2019  2018  2017  2016  2015  2014  2013   2012  2011  2010  2009  Featured publications #   MOEA/D: decomposition-based EMO MCDM: preference learning and decision-making CO: constrained optimization SE: software engineering   MOEA/D  Stable Matching Based Selection in Evolutionary Multiobjective Optimization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects #  Under construction  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2009/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2009 #  Conference #    A Novel Algorithm for Non-dominated Hypervolume-based Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li, Jinhua Zheng, Miqing Li, Cong Zhou, Hui Lv
Proc. of 2009 IEEE International Conference on Systems, Mans and Cybernetics (SMC’09), IEEE Press: p. 5220–5226, December 2009.
  10.1109/ICSMC.2009.5345983
[ PDF] [ BiB]
  An Spanning Tree Based Method For Pruning Non-Dominated Solutions in Multi- Objective Optimization Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2010/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2010 #  Journal #   A Novel Slicing Based Algorithm to Calculate Hypervolume for Multi-Objective Optimization Problems
Ke Li, Jinhua Zheng, Miqing Li, Cong Zhou, Hui Lv
ICIC Express Letters: An International Journal of Research and Surveys, 4(4): 1113–1120, 2010.
[ PDF] [ BiB]  Conference #    Enhancing Diversity for Average Ranking Method in Evolutionary Many-Objective Optimization
Miqing Li, Jinhua Zheng, Ke Li, Qizhao Yuan, Ruimin Shen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2011/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2011 #  Conference #    Combining Interpretable Fuzzy Rule-based Classifiers via Multi-Objective Hierarchical Evolutionary Algorithm
Jingjing Cao, Hanli Wang, Sam Kwong, Ke Li
Proc. of 2011 IEEE International Conference on Systems, Mans and Cybernetics (SMC’11), IEEE Press: p. 1771–1776, October 2011.
  10.1109/ICSMC.2011.6083928
[ PDF] [ BiB]
  JGBL paradigm: A Novel Strategy to Enhance the Exploration Ability of NSGA-II
Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Kim-Fung Man</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2012/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2012 #  Journal #   Achieving Balance Between Proximity and Diversity in Multi-objective Evolutionary Algorithm
Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Jingjing Cao, Miqing Li, Jinhua Zheng, Ruimin Shen
Information Sciences (INS), 182(1): 220–242, 2012.
  10.1016/j.ins.2011.08.027
[ PDF] [ BiB]  Conference #    Multi-Objective Differential Evolution with Self-Navigation
Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Ran Wang, Jingjing Cao, Imre J. Rudas
Proc. of 2012 IEEE International Conference on Systems, Mans and Cybernetics (SMC’12), IEEE Press: p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2013/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2013 #  Journal #   Learning Paradigm Based on Jumping Genes: A General Framework for Enhancing Exploration in Evolutionary Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Ran Wang, Kit-Sang Tang, Kim-Fung Man
Information Sciences (INS), 226: 1–22, 2013.
  10.1016/j.ins.2012.11.002
[ PDF] [ Code] [ BiB]  Conference #   Evolving Extreme Learning Machine Paradigm with Adaptive Operator Selection and Parameter Control
Ke Li, Ran Wang, Sam Kwong, Jingjing Cao</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2014/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2014 #  Journal #    Stable Matching Based Selection in Evolutionary Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li, Qingfu Zhang, Sam Kwong, Miqing Li, Ran Wang
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC). 18(6): 909–923, 2014.
  10.1109/TEVC.2013.2293776
[ PDF] [ Code] [ BiB]
  Adaptive Operator Selection with Bandits for Multiobjective Evolutionary Algorithm Based on Decomposition
Ke Li, Álvaro Fialho, Sam Kwong, Qingfu Zhang
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2015/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2015 #  Journal #    An Evolutionary Many-Objective Optimization Algorithm Based on Dominance and Decomposition
Ke Li, Kalyanmoy Deb, Qingfu Zhang, Sam Kwong
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC), 19(5): 694–716, 2015.
  10.1109/TEVC.2014.2373386
[ PDF] [ Code] [ BiB]
  Interrelationship-Based Selection for Decomposition Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Qingfu Zhang, Kalyanmoy Deb
IEEE Trans. Cybernetics (TCYB), 45(10): 2076-2088, 2015
  10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2016/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2016 #  Journal #  Personalized Search for Social Media via Dominating Verbal Context
Haoran Xie, Xiaodong Li, Tao Wang, Li Chen, Ke Li, Fu Lee Wang, Yi Cai, Qing Li, Huaqing Min
Neurocomputing (NEUCOM). 172: 27–37, 2016.
  10.1016/j.neucom.2014.12.109
[ PDF] [ BiB]
Conference #  Variable Interactions in Multi-Objective Optimization Problems
Ke Li, Mohammad Nabi Omidvar, Kalyanmoy Deb, Xin Yao
Proc. of the 14th International Conference on Parallel Problem Solving from Nature (PPSN’16), Springer, LNCS, Volume 9921: p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2017/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2017 #  Journal #    Efficient Non-domination Level Update Method for Steady-State Evolutionary Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li, Kalyanmoy Deb, Qingfu Zhang, Qiang Zhang
IEEE Trans. Cybernetics (TCYB), 47(9): 2838–2849, 2017.
  10.1109/TCYB.2016.2621008
[ PDF] [ Supplementary] [ Code] [ BiB]
  Matching-Based Selection with Incomplete Lists for Decomposition Multi-Objective Optimization
Mengyuan Wu+, Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Yu Zhou, Qingfu Zhang
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC), 21(4): 554–568, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2018/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2018 #  Journal #    R-Metric: Evaluating the Performance of Preference-Based Evolutionary Multi-Objective Optimization Using Reference Points
Ke Li, Kalyanmoy Deb, Xin Yao
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC), 22(6): 821–835, 2018.
   10.1109/TEVC.2017.2737781
[ PDF] [ Supplementary] [ Code] [ BiB]
  Integration of Preferences in Decomposition Multiobjective Optimization
Ke Li*, Renzhi Chen*+, Geyong Min, Xin Yao
IEEE Trans. Cybernetics (TCYB), 48(12): 3359–3370, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2019/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2019 #  Journal #    Learning to Decompose: A Paradigm for Decomposition-Based Multi-Objective Optimization
Mengyuan Wu+, Ke Li, Sam Kwong, Qingfu Zhang, Jun Zhang
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC), 23(3): 376–390, 2019.
  10.1109/TEVC.2018.2865931
[PDF] [Supplementary] [Code] [ BiB]
  Interactive Decomposition Multi-Objective Optimization via Progressively Learned Value Functions
Ke Li*, Renzhi Chen*+, Dragan Savic, Xin Yao
IEEE Trans. Fuzzy Systems (TFS), 27(5): 845–860, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/2020/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  2020 #  Journal #    Does Preference Always Help? A Holistic Study on Preference-Based Evolutionary Multi-Objective Optimisation Using Reference Points
Ke Li, Minhui Liao+, Kalyanmoy Deb, Geyong Min, Xin Yao
IEEE Trans. Evolutionary Computation (TEVC), 24(6): 1078-1096, 2020.
  10.1109/TEVC.2020.2987559
[ PDF] [ Project] [BiB]
  Reference Point Based Multi-Objective Optimization of Reservoir Operation: a Comparison of Three Algorithms
Rong Tang, Ke Li, Wei Ding, Yuntao Wang, Huicheng Zhou, Guangtao Fu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/new/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications_year/new/</guid>
      <description>Publications #  To appear #  Journal #   Bayesian Network Based Label Correlation Analysis For Multi-label Classifier Chain
Ran Wang, Suhe Ye, Ke Li, Sam Kwong
Information Sciences
[PDF] [BiB]  Conference #    An Improved Two-Archive Evolutionary Algorithm for Constrained Multi-Objective Optimization
Xinyu Shan+, Ke Li
Proc. of the 11th International Conference on Evolutionary Multi-Criterion Optimization (EMO&#39;21), March, 2021
[PDF] [BiB]
  Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning based Multi-Microgrid System Optimisation Problem</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadlines</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/misc/ddl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/misc/ddl/</guid>
      <description>Deadlines #  Here are some important deadlines for the major conferences in artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI &amp;amp; ML), software engineering (SE) and evolutionary computation (EC) domains.
AI &amp;amp; ML  IJCAI 2021: January 20, 2021 ICML 2021: February 4, 2021 UAI 2021: February 19, 2021 NIPS 2021: May 27, 2021 AAAI 2022: TBD ICLR 2022: TBD AISTAS 2022: TBD SDM 2022: TBD  SE  ISSTA 2021: Jan 29, 2021 FSE 2021: February 25, 2021 ASE 2021: April 23, 2021 ICSE 2022: September 3, 2021  EC  GECCO 2021: February 4, 2021 IJCNN: February 10, 2021 CEC 2021: February 21, 2021 SMC 2021: April 5, 2021 FOGA 2021: May 7, 2021 SSCI 2021: August 6, 2021   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/grants/</guid>
      <description>Grants #      hr.dashed { border-top: 1px dashed #bbb; } .grid-container { display: grid; grid-template-columns: 40% 60%; grid-gap: 5px; background-color: transparent; padding: 5px; }  We are grateful to have been generously supported by or closely working with the following funding bodies and industrial partners.
 Ongoing  Amazon Research Award: AWS AI Call, Many Hands Make Work Light: Multi-task Deep Semantic Learning for Testing Web Application Firewalls, PI, $10,000, 2021-2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEEE DTEC</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/misc/dtec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/misc/dtec/</guid>
      <description>IEEE CIS Task Force 12 #  Task Force on Decomposition-based Techniques in Evolutionary Computation Objectives #  As the name suggests, the basic idea of the decomposition-based technique is to transform the original complex problem into simplified subproblem(s) so as to facilitate the optimization. Decomposition-based techniques have been widely used for solving both single- and multi-objective optimization problems. More specifically, in single-objective optimization, especially for the large-scale scenarios, which consider a tremendous amount of decision variables, the decomposition-based technique contains three aspects: 1) analyzing and understanding the fitness landscape and modularity structure of the underlying problem; 2) decomposing the original complex problem into several loosely coupled or independent subproblems based on the learnt characteristics; 3) using a meta-heuristic to solve these subproblems in a sequential or concurrent manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/news/</guid>
      <description>News Archive #  2020 #  Dec   Our paper on Bayesian Network Based Label Correlation Analysis For Multi-label Classifier Chain has been accepted for publication in Information Sciences. Congratulations to my collaborators! Dec 8
  There are multiple openings in our lab for PhD students 2021 entry. The studentships are available for both UK/EU and international students. Please have a look at vacancies and feel free to contact with me for more details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/members/</guid>
      <description>Members #      hr.dashed { border-top: 1px dashed #bbb; } .grid-container { display: grid; grid-template-columns: 15% 35% 15% 35%; grid-gap: 15px; background-color: transparent; padding: 5px; align-content: left; }   Lookup table of acronyms in this page. &amp;#43;   EMO: evolutionary multi-objective optimization BO: Bayesian optimization BLO: bi-level optimization MFO: multi-fidelity optimization CO: constrained optimization DO: dynamic optimization MCM: Monte Carlo method    LA: landscape analysis TL: transfer learning MTL: multi-task learning LL: life-long learning GP: Gaussian processes NLP: natural language processing SE: software engineering VNF: virtual network functions         Faculty #   Dr Ke Li (UKRI FLF)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications #      hr.dashed { border-top: 1px dashed #bbb; } .grid-container { display: grid; grid-template-columns: 40% 60%; grid-gap: 5px; background-color: transparent; padding: 5px; }   The copyrights of published papers are transferred to publishers. Misuse of any material posted here may result in plagiarism. means equal contribution. + means my current/previous student or visitor. * means equal contribution   To appear #   Technical Report #   Posterior Decision-Making Based on Decomposition-Driven Knee Point Identification</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading Group</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/research/readinggroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/research/readinggroup/</guid>
      <description>Reading Group #     The paper reading group meets weekly during the semester to discuss papers. Participation is open to all, guests are always welcome; if you are interested in receiving invitations contact the organizer.   More about our reading group culture &amp;#43;  Each week we will discuss a different paper. The paper to discuss is announced about one week in advance by the organizer. All participants are expected to read the paper before the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacancies</title>
      <link>https://example.com/docs/home/vacancies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/docs/home/vacancies/</guid>
      <description>Vacancies #     We very much welcome and support applications from underrepresented groups and from people of all shapes, shades, and genders. If you are uncertain about your possible role in our team, please do not hesitate to get in touch with Ke Li.
PhD There are multiple opportunities available at the University of Exeter to fund your PhD study.
 China Scholarship Council (Chinese Students): The University of Exeter is proud to offer up to 50 full-time PhD scholarships in collaboration with the China Scholarship Council (CSC).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
